<!-- Answer Record of Mr. Monkey V2.5c-->
<!-- Generated in Fri Apr 06 14:24:20 CST 2012 -->

<nhmonkey.Recorder_-Form>
  <bookID>16</bookID>
  <unitID>2</unitID>
  <sectionID>3</sectionID>
  <sisterID>4</sisterID>
  <testID>3.4</testID>
  <inputs>
    <nhmonkey.Recorder_-Input>
      <name>Item_833_0</name>
      <value>Natasha made herself stand out in the group interview by acting as the leader in her group.</value>
    </nhmonkey.Recorder_-Input>
    <nhmonkey.Recorder_-Input>
      <name>Item_834_0</name>
      <value>To be successful, you need a careful plan, good luck, help at the right time, and above all, hard work.</value>
    </nhmonkey.Recorder_-Input>
    <nhmonkey.Recorder_-Input>
      <name>Item_835_0</name>
      <value>They are not doing this to gain recognition or money; they are doing this for the sake of society.</value>
    </nhmonkey.Recorder_-Input>
    <nhmonkey.Recorder_-Input>
      <name>Item_836_0</name>
      <value>It was actually what he said rather than what he did that made me sad.</value>
    </nhmonkey.Recorder_-Input>
    <nhmonkey.Recorder_-Input>
      <name>Item_837_0</name>
      <value>Once my mother sets her mind on something, it will be very hard to stop her.</value>
    </nhmonkey.Recorder_-Input>
    <nhmonkey.Recorder_-Input>
      <name>Item_838_0</name>
      <value>Years of research had set the stage for their success in their field.</value>
    </nhmonkey.Recorder_-Input>
    <nhmonkey.Recorder_-Input>
      <name>Item_839_0</name>
      <value>Local people are used to the phenomenon, so they are not surprised at all.</value>
    </nhmonkey.Recorder_-Input>
    <nhmonkey.Recorder_-Input>
      <name>Item_840_0</name>
      <value>Today at this meeting we are going to focus on the question of air pollution.</value>
    </nhmonkey.Recorder_-Input>
    <nhmonkey.Recorder_-Input>
      <name>Item_841_0</name>
      <value>He never expected that his best friend would charge him with cheating in the exam.</value>
    </nhmonkey.Recorder_-Input>
    <nhmonkey.Recorder_-Input>
      <name>Item_842_0</name>
      <value>His parents were so strict with him in his studies that he had little time to participate in any activities outside of class.</value>
    </nhmonkey.Recorder_-Input>
    <nhmonkey.Recorder_-Input>
      <name>Item_843_0</name>
      <value>I was interested to see the elephants stripping trees of leaves with their long trunks.</value>
    </nhmonkey.Recorder_-Input>
    <nhmonkey.Recorder_-Input>
      <name>Item_844_0</name>
      <value>I had told you again and again to find a more suitable person for this position, but you simply wouldn&apos;t hear of it.</value>
    </nhmonkey.Recorder_-Input>
    <nhmonkey.Recorder_-Input>
      <name>Item_845_0</name>
      <value>A trained dog can act as a guide to a blind person.</value>
    </nhmonkey.Recorder_-Input>
  </inputs>
</nhmonkey.Recorder_-Form>