<!-- Answer Record of Mr. Monkey V2.5c-->
<!-- Generated in Sun Apr 08 22:06:46 CST 2012 -->

<nhmonkey.Recorder_-Form>
  <bookID>16</bookID>
  <unitID>9</unitID>
  <sectionID>3</sectionID>
  <sisterID>4</sisterID>
  <testID>3.4</testID>
  <inputs>
    <nhmonkey.Recorder_-Input>
      <name>Item_880_0</name>
      <value>He is a man who prefers action to words.</value>
    </nhmonkey.Recorder_-Input>
    <nhmonkey.Recorder_-Input>
      <name>Item_881_0</name>
      <value>The child was told time and time again not to go near the railway but he didn&apos;t seem to listen.</value>
    </nhmonkey.Recorder_-Input>
    <nhmonkey.Recorder_-Input>
      <name>Item_882_0</name>
      <value>John studied hard before the examination and it paid off. He made an A.</value>
    </nhmonkey.Recorder_-Input>
    <nhmonkey.Recorder_-Input>
      <name>Item_883_0</name>
      <value>In the meantime, focus your attention on something that you&apos;re really interested in and never quit.</value>
    </nhmonkey.Recorder_-Input>
    <nhmonkey.Recorder_-Input>
      <name>Item_884_0</name>
      <value>With reference to the school uniform policy, there were various thoughts and feelings among students.</value>
    </nhmonkey.Recorder_-Input>
    <nhmonkey.Recorder_-Input>
      <name>Item_885_0</name>
      <value>Would you please look at my paper and give your suggestions about it?</value>
    </nhmonkey.Recorder_-Input>
    <nhmonkey.Recorder_-Input>
      <name>Item_886_0</name>
      <value>I felt obliged to go over there to say sorry to him as I didn&apos;t want to hurt his feelings.</value>
    </nhmonkey.Recorder_-Input>
    <nhmonkey.Recorder_-Input>
      <name>Item_887_0</name>
      <value>It only took about 30 minutes before the high school was filled up with the survivors of the disaster.</value>
    </nhmonkey.Recorder_-Input>
    <nhmonkey.Recorder_-Input>
      <name>Item_888_0</name>
      <value>He slipped and broke his leg. As a result, he will have to be away from school for two or three months.</value>
    </nhmonkey.Recorder_-Input>
    <nhmonkey.Recorder_-Input>
      <name>Item_889_0</name>
      <value>This newly invented device will help those people who tend to get themselves injured.</value>
    </nhmonkey.Recorder_-Input>
    <nhmonkey.Recorder_-Input>
      <name>Item_890_0</name>
      <value>Whatever the problems in their personal lives, their thoughts can find paths that lead to inner satisfaction.</value>
    </nhmonkey.Recorder_-Input>
    <nhmonkey.Recorder_-Input>
      <name>Item_891_0</name>
      <value>Sometimes I think how ready we are to take offense at each other by looking out only for our own interests, or envying someone else for their good things.</value>
    </nhmonkey.Recorder_-Input>
    <nhmonkey.Recorder_-Input>
      <name>Item_892_0</name>
      <value>Don&apos;t feel frustrated easily and smile often as your participation and efforts will finally pay off.</value>
    </nhmonkey.Recorder_-Input>
  </inputs>
</nhmonkey.Recorder_-Form>