<!-- Answer Record of Mr. Monkey V2.6b-->
<!-- Generated in Thu May 31 16:04:59 CST 2012 -->

<nhmonkey.Recorder_-Form>
  <bookID>17</bookID>
  <unitID>10</unitID>
  <sectionID>3</sectionID>
  <sisterID>1</sisterID>
  <testID>3.1</testID>
  <inputs>
    <nhmonkey.Recorder_-Input>
      <name>Item_0</name>
      <value>Denotation: the curved or circular shape Connotation(s): the act of going around somewhere. The implied meaning is that the policeman was going around the area, trying doors and consequently seeing now and then the lights of an emergency dental office or something of the sort.</value>
    </nhmonkey.Recorder_-Input>
    <nhmonkey.Recorder_-Input>
      <name>Item_1</name>
      <value>Denotation: make a deep hollow sound Connotation(s): loudly spread to the streets. The implied meaning is that the streets were quiet, and that even bars were careful not to get their loud music into the streets.</value>
    </nhmonkey.Recorder_-Input>
    <nhmonkey.Recorder_-Input>
      <name>Item_2</name>
      <value>Denotation: say what medicine a sick person should or must have Connotation(s): The West is tough enough to make a man strong. Here the West is compared to a doctor.</value>
    </nhmonkey.Recorder_-Input>
    <nhmonkey.Recorder_-Input>
      <name>Item_3</name>
      <value>Denotation: (of an army or the police) surround a place and try to gain control of it or force someone to come out of it Connotation(s): blow hard on the city streets. The implied meaning of the sentence is that the wind was very strong and blew hard on the city streets like an army making a fierce attack on its enemy.</value>
    </nhmonkey.Recorder_-Input>
    <nhmonkey.Recorder_-Input>
      <name>Item_4</name>
      <value>Denotation: production Connotation(s): his achievements. The implied meaning of the sentence is that the man from the West was boasting about how he made his &quot;achievements&quot;: rising to the top by means legal or illegal, etc.</value>
    </nhmonkey.Recorder_-Input>
    <nhmonkey.Recorder_-Input>
      <name>Item_5</name>
      <value>Denotation: (cause to) change shape, the true or intended meaning, or direction Connotation(s): change a good man into a bad one. The use of the word &quot;twist&quot; suggests that the man was not only changed in appearance but also in nature.</value>
    </nhmonkey.Recorder_-Input>
  </inputs>
</nhmonkey.Recorder_-Form>