<!-- Answer Record of Mr. Monkey V2.6b-->
<!-- Generated in Thu May 31 14:09:46 CST 2012 -->

<nhmonkey.Recorder_-Form>
  <bookID>17</bookID>
  <unitID>4</unitID>
  <sectionID>3</sectionID>
  <sisterID>1</sisterID>
  <testID>3.1</testID>
  <inputs>
    <nhmonkey.Recorder_-Input>
      <name>Item_0</name>
      <value>To crush is to press something so hard that it is damaged or destroyed. Here Mary compares herself to a thing that is too weak to resist the pressure, i.e., the harsh words from publishers. Mary admits that she is extremely upset.</value>
    </nhmonkey.Recorder_-Input>
    <nhmonkey.Recorder_-Input>
      <name>Item_1</name>
      <value>At the very beginning Engelbreit did not expect to draw greeting cards; she aimed high. Now that she was told her style was better suited for drawing greeting cards, she felt it was a comedown from high expectation. To her, drawing greeting cards was a fall from her life&apos;s goal.</value>
    </nhmonkey.Recorder_-Input>
    <nhmonkey.Recorder_-Input>
      <name>Item_2</name>
      <value>The card is personified. As we know, a card cannot boast. Only the creator of the card boasts. However, the writer means to say that the card is communicating a proud message.</value>
    </nhmonkey.Recorder_-Input>
    <nhmonkey.Recorder_-Input>
      <name>Item_3</name>
      <value>Acid means having a sour or bitter taste. When one has an acid tongue, he or she is very bitter to others, that is, he or she is very critical of others.</value>
    </nhmonkey.Recorder_-Input>
    <nhmonkey.Recorder_-Input>
      <name>Item_4</name>
      <value>A trademark is a special name, sign, word, etc. marked on a product; it is a special sign or a distinctive characteristic. Now being cute is Mary&apos;s distinctive feature.</value>
    </nhmonkey.Recorder_-Input>
    <nhmonkey.Recorder_-Input>
      <name>Item_5</name>
      <value>A core is the central part of certain fruit. A core of one&apos;s life is the most important part of one&apos;s life. The whole sentence means Engelbreit treasures old-fashioned art and values most.</value>
    </nhmonkey.Recorder_-Input>
    <nhmonkey.Recorder_-Input>
      <name>Item_6</name>
      <value>When one puts his or her feet firmly on the ground, he or she is down-to-earth. In other words, he or she is very realistic and practical.</value>
    </nhmonkey.Recorder_-Input>
    <nhmonkey.Recorder_-Input>
      <name>Item_7</name>
      <value>When you say an artistic work takes off, you mean it begins to be successful.</value>
    </nhmonkey.Recorder_-Input>
  </inputs>
</nhmonkey.Recorder_-Form>