<!-- Answer Record of Mr. Monkey V2.6b-->
<!-- Generated in Thu May 31 14:56:19 CST 2012 -->

<nhmonkey.Recorder_-Form>
  <bookID>17</bookID>
  <unitID>6</unitID>
  <sectionID>3</sectionID>
  <sisterID>4</sisterID>
  <testID>3.4</testID>
  <inputs>
    <nhmonkey.Recorder_-Input>
      <name>Item_1018_0</name>
      <value>Now that I am retired, I find I am spending more and more time on charity work, which I am very happy to take part in.</value>
    </nhmonkey.Recorder_-Input>
    <nhmonkey.Recorder_-Input>
      <name>Item_1019_0</name>
      <value>His suggestions are in harmony with the aims of the project.</value>
    </nhmonkey.Recorder_-Input>
    <nhmonkey.Recorder_-Input>
      <name>Item_1020_0</name>
      <value>In other words, 95 percent of the students have passed the entrance examination and been admitted to universities.</value>
    </nhmonkey.Recorder_-Input>
    <nhmonkey.Recorder_-Input>
      <name>Item_1021_0</name>
      <value>We go abroad for a week or ten days every year, but I think we have a very simple life compared with many.</value>
    </nhmonkey.Recorder_-Input>
    <nhmonkey.Recorder_-Input>
      <name>Item_1022_0</name>
      <value>Since coal is formed from plants, which are chemically very complicated, its own chemical make-up is very complex.</value>
    </nhmonkey.Recorder_-Input>
    <nhmonkey.Recorder_-Input>
      <name>Item_1023_0</name>
      <value>During his stay in the countryside, he took to smoking.</value>
    </nhmonkey.Recorder_-Input>
    <nhmonkey.Recorder_-Input>
      <name>Item_1024_0</name>
      <value>The father was ignorant of the boy&apos;s secrets.</value>
    </nhmonkey.Recorder_-Input>
    <nhmonkey.Recorder_-Input>
      <name>Item_1025_0</name>
      <value>The earthquake that took place last week brought about ten thousand deaths and destruction of half of the buildings in the area.</value>
    </nhmonkey.Recorder_-Input>
    <nhmonkey.Recorder_-Input>
      <name>Item_1026_0</name>
      <value>The lawyer said to the old man: &quot;If you die before you have made a will, the law will decide the distribution of your property, which may not be in accordance with your wishes.&quot;</value>
    </nhmonkey.Recorder_-Input>
    <nhmonkey.Recorder_-Input>
      <name>Item_1027_0</name>
      <value>The changes that have taken place over the past several years―both in terms of the marketplace and in the changing expectations of our patients―increasingly require that our physicians be kind to their patients.</value>
    </nhmonkey.Recorder_-Input>
    <nhmonkey.Recorder_-Input>
      <name>Item_1028_0</name>
      <value>It may seem a laughably small sum compared to the salary you&apos;ve been used to, and is an impossibly small amount to survive on.</value>
    </nhmonkey.Recorder_-Input>
    <nhmonkey.Recorder_-Input>
      <name>Item_1029_0</name>
      <value>Organizations and individuals must prepare to take advantage of the business opportunities that lie ahead.</value>
    </nhmonkey.Recorder_-Input>
  </inputs>
</nhmonkey.Recorder_-Form>