<!-- Answer Record of Mr. Monkey V2.4-4-->
<!-- Generated in Fri Mar 16 17:29:41 CST 2012 -->

<nhmonkey.Recorder_-Form>
  <bookID>18</bookID>
  <unitID>5</unitID>
  <sectionID>3</sectionID>
  <sisterID>4</sisterID>
  <testID>3.4</testID>
  <inputs>
    <nhmonkey.Recorder_-Input>
      <name>Item_434_0</name>
      <value>When he received the admission notice from the university, he knew it was time he struck out on his own.</value>
    </nhmonkey.Recorder_-Input>
    <nhmonkey.Recorder_-Input>
      <name>Item_435_0</name>
      <value>I had to keep the video camera readily accessible in case I saw something that needed to be filmed.</value>
    </nhmonkey.Recorder_-Input>
    <nhmonkey.Recorder_-Input>
      <name>Item_436_0</name>
      <value>Every time she tried to argue with her identical twin Katie, she would end up crying her eyes out.</value>
    </nhmonkey.Recorder_-Input>
    <nhmonkey.Recorder_-Input>
      <name>Item_437_0</name>
      <value>Serious violence has sprung from the conflict over insignificant, irritating differences.</value>
    </nhmonkey.Recorder_-Input>
    <nhmonkey.Recorder_-Input>
      <name>Item_438_0</name>
      <value>There are many people who believe sincerely that you can train children for life without resorting to punishment.</value>
    </nhmonkey.Recorder_-Input>
    <nhmonkey.Recorder_-Input>
      <name>Item_439_0</name>
      <value>Alan signed a dorm contract with his roommate to head off possible conflicts.</value>
    </nhmonkey.Recorder_-Input>
    <nhmonkey.Recorder_-Input>
      <name>Item_440_0</name>
      <value>He was required to fill in a form before the job interview.</value>
    </nhmonkey.Recorder_-Input>
    <nhmonkey.Recorder_-Input>
      <name>Item_441_0</name>
      <value>Her major concern is how she will make sure the people on the teams get along with one another.</value>
    </nhmonkey.Recorder_-Input>
    <nhmonkey.Recorder_-Input>
      <name>Item_442_0</name>
      <value>Against all the odds, it has worked, and this is a measure of just how strong they both were as individuals when they came to the marriage ten years ago.</value>
    </nhmonkey.Recorder_-Input>
    <nhmonkey.Recorder_-Input>
      <name>Item_443_0</name>
      <value>What I&apos;d like to do is to help them to see that they don&apos;t need to give up on the computer, that they can actually be the master of it.</value>
    </nhmonkey.Recorder_-Input>
  </inputs>
</nhmonkey.Recorder_-Form>