<!-- Answer Record of Mr. Monkey V2.4-4-->
<!-- Generated in Fri Mar 16 19:34:05 CST 2012 -->

<nhmonkey.Recorder_-Form>
  <bookID>18</bookID>
  <unitID>9</unitID>
  <sectionID>3</sectionID>
  <sisterID>4</sisterID>
  <testID>3.4</testID>
  <inputs>
    <nhmonkey.Recorder_-Input>
      <name>Item_654_0</name>
      <value>According to the survey, students and children accounted for more than 50% of the visitors to Euro Disneyland last year.</value>
    </nhmonkey.Recorder_-Input>
    <nhmonkey.Recorder_-Input>
      <name>Item_655_0</name>
      <value>These employees thought banning moustaches and beards amounted to violating their individual rights.</value>
    </nhmonkey.Recorder_-Input>
    <nhmonkey.Recorder_-Input>
      <name>Item_656_0</name>
      <value>Most of the student guides work for the theme park on a voluntary basis.</value>
    </nhmonkey.Recorder_-Input>
    <nhmonkey.Recorder_-Input>
      <name>Item_657_0</name>
      <value>The theme park is gearing up for the invasion of tourists in the coming summer vacation period.</value>
    </nhmonkey.Recorder_-Input>
    <nhmonkey.Recorder_-Input>
      <name>Item_658_0</name>
      <value>Uncertainty again hangs over the company&apos;s current financial conditions and many stockholders are selling its shares.</value>
    </nhmonkey.Recorder_-Input>
    <nhmonkey.Recorder_-Input>
      <name>Item_659_0</name>
      <value>Manufacturing companies spend millions of pounds trying to convince customers that their products are superior to those of other companies.</value>
    </nhmonkey.Recorder_-Input>
    <nhmonkey.Recorder_-Input>
      <name>Item_660_0</name>
      <value>The union representative argued that the practices of banning moustaches, excess weight and short skirts were not in line with French labor law.</value>
    </nhmonkey.Recorder_-Input>
    <nhmonkey.Recorder_-Input>
      <name>Item_661_0</name>
      <value>The stock prices of the company are too high now, but they are going to be all right in the long term.</value>
    </nhmonkey.Recorder_-Input>
    <nhmonkey.Recorder_-Input>
      <name>Item_662_0</name>
      <value>He wrote to warn me against going to the east coast because it was so full of tourists.</value>
    </nhmonkey.Recorder_-Input>
    <nhmonkey.Recorder_-Input>
      <name>Item_663_0</name>
      <value>Success doesn&apos;t only depend on what you do. What you don&apos;t do is equally important.</value>
    </nhmonkey.Recorder_-Input>
  </inputs>
</nhmonkey.Recorder_-Form>